It's just really indicative of the facts that we are living in a police state and it's only
going to get worse. You know, the police here have in many ways become, well, they're not
protecting people, they're protecting property. But then they're also just carrying out racism
on a regular basis. Many of them have been trained by IOF soldiers from Israel. And as we know,
they are looking to build cop cities all over this nation where they will be militarizing
police forces in compounds that in some cases are being built on college campuses.
Wow.
So apparently they're looking to build one on an HBCU campus in Baltimore.
What?
They're also looking to build one on the UNT campus in Dallas, Texas.
And they've already broken ground in Tennessee.
So what I want to make sure to tell everybody, though, is that if you're listening to us and
your state has a vote coming up, please be careful because the language that they are using to
get your bond money, your tax dollars put towards these is very duplicitous language.
It's not very clear. And you end up voting for something that is not what you think you're
voting for. So they'll say that, oh, you know, this is for public safety.
You know, they'll use language like that.
OK.
While I was in Dallas, I went canvassing with the Stop Cop City Dallas organization
around the neighborhood where they're going to build where they're looking to build cop cities.
So we went to the church. We went to people's doors and knocked on doors.
We, you know, put flyers on people's cars to let them know about this vote that's coming up.
And I'm going to try and get the young lady who I was working with to come on the show
because it's not just about what's happening in Dallas or Texas.
I mean, or Tennessee, like they're looking to build cop cities in 68 cities all across the nation.
Yeah.
So, you know, I think it's just really important that folks get up.
And of course, Atlanta is the first city that we saw a real movement or we're seeing a real
movement around just preventing cop cities.
So this right here will only get worse.
So why should black people care?
Because complacency is a part of their playbook.
They're counting on us to be desensitized to police corruption.
And we need to continue to be surprised every single time.